[
    {
        "front": "げんかん",
        "back": "Entrance Hall",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "トイレ",
        "back": "Toilet",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "おふろ",
        "back": "Bathroom",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんめんじょ",
        "back": "Washroom",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいどころ",
        "back": "Kitchen",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょくどう",
        "back": "Dining Hall",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "いま",
        "back": "Living Room",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんしつ",
        "back": "Bedroom",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ろうか",
        "back": "Gallery",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ベランダ",
        "back": "Balcony",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "おくります",
        "back": "To send, to gift",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "おわります",
        "back": "To finish",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "あげます",
        "back": "To give",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "もらいます",
        "back": "To receive",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "かします",
        "back": "To lend",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "かります",
        "back": "To borrow",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいます",
        "back": "To purchase",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "かきます",
        "back": "To write",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ならいます",
        "back": "To learn, to practice (by someone)",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "おしえます",
        "back": "To teach",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "くれます",
        "back": "to give (family or friend)",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "まなびます",
        "back": "To learn",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "て",
        "back": "Hand/s",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "はし",
        "back": "Chopsticks",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "はさみ",
        "back": "Scissors",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "かみ",
        "back": "Paper",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "はな",
        "back": "Flowers",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "えんぴつ",
        "back": "Pencil",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "けしごむ",
        "back": "Eraser",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "シャツ",
        "back": "Shirt",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "プレゼント",
        "back": "Present, Gift",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "にもつ",
        "back": "Luggage, Bag",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "おかね",
        "back": "Money",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "きっぷ",
        "back": "Ticket (Bus, train)",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "これから",
        "back": "From now on",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "あね",
        "back": "(My) Elder sister",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "おねえさん",
        "back": "Someone else’s elder sister",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "あに",
        "back": "(My) Elder brother",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "おにいさん",
        "back": "Someone else’s elder brother",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "おっと",
        "back": "(My) Husband",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごしゅじん",
        "back": "Someone else’s husband",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "つま",
        "back": "(My) Wife",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "おくさん",
        "back": "Someone else’s wife",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "むすめ",
        "back": "(My) Daughter",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "むすめさん",
        "back": "Someone else’s Daughter",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "むすこ",
        "back": "(My) son",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "むすこさん",
        "back": "Someone else’s son",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "がんばります",
        "back": "I will do my best",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "すばらしい",
        "back": "Wonderful, amazing, admirable",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ところで",
        "back": "By the way (while changing a topic)",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほしい",
        "back": "Want, Desire (for Noun)",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "~たい",
        "back": "Want, Desire (for Verb)",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "てんき",
        "back": "Weather, Climate",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "まんが",
        "back": "Comic book",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ところ",
        "back": "Place",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "かけます",
        "back": "to call",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "はがき",
        "back": "Postcard",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "だれ に",
        "back": "‘to whom’",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "テレビ",
        "back": "TV",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ラジオ",
        "back": "Radio",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "レポート",
        "back": "Report",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "カード",
        "back": "Card",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "かぞく",
        "back": "Family",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "もう",
        "back": "Already",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    },
    {
        "front": "まだ",
        "back": "Still, Not yet",
        "chapter": "N5 C10"
    }
]